《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously on AMC's "The Walking Dead..."
你告诉我们要准备抗争
You told us to get ready to fight
现在我能了
and I can now.
玛姬说她的人能搞定救世军
Maggie said that her people could take care of the Saviors.
但他们只是让我们的社区陷入险境
But so far all they've done is put our community at risk.
我想让你们帮我劝以西结攻击救世军
I'm asking you to help convince Ezekiel to attack the Saviors
灭掉他们
and destroy them.
我们会胜利的
We'll win,
我们要等待合适的时机
we need to wait for the right moment.
我们需要你
We need you.
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
翻译     艾瑞卡 小僵僵首P好激动 送小孩
校对     送小孩
时间轴     加森  涛涛  啾啾啾
后期     送小哥  拉图
圣经
总监     送小孩
核对下
Just checking.
行尸走肉
『第七季  第九集』
不  绝对不行
No! No way in hell.
协议不是这样的
That was not the deal.
你们发誓能干掉救世军
You people swore you could take the Saviors out,
你们失败了
and you failed.
所以我们的协议终结了
So any arrangement we had is now done --
无效了
null and void.
我们不是贸易伙伴  不是朋友
We aren't trade partners, we aren't friends,
从未谋面
and we never met.
懂吗
Hmm?
我们不认识
We don't know each other.
我不欠你什么
I owe you nothing.
实际上  你欠我的  因为我收留了难民
In fact, you owe me for taking in the refugees,
我个人冒了很大的风险
at great personal risk.
你那时真勇敢  待在这里
Oh, you were very brave staying in here
而玛姬和萨沙救了这里
while Maggie and Sasha saved this place.
你的勇气真是鼓舞人心
Your courage was inspiring.
你不是为我工作吗
Hey, don't you work for me?
我们不是朋友吗
Aren't we friends?
格雷戈里  我们已经开始了
Gregory, we already started this.
-是你开始的  -是我们
- You started it. - We did.
我们会赢的
And we're gonna win.
这些人是凶手啊
These are killers.
你就想这样活着吗
Is this how you want to live?
受他们的控制  他们还杀你们的人
Under their thumb, killing your people?
有时候我们无法选择
S-Sometimes we don't get to choose
生活的方式
what our life looks like.
有时候  瑞克
Sometimes, Ricky,
你得珍惜眼前的一切
you have to count the blessings you have.
我们能分出多少人
How many people can we spare?
这里有多少人可以战斗
How many people here can fight?
我们
"We"?
我都不知道我们有多少人  玛格丽特
I don't even know how many people we have, Margaret.
这重要吗
And does it even matter?
我是说
I mean...
你们想做什么
...w-w-what are you gonna do?
组一队种高粱的农民吗
Start a platoon of sorghum farmers?
因为我们只有这种人
'Cause that's what we got.
他们种庄稼  不想战斗
They grow things. They're not gonna want to fight.
你错了
You're wrong.
当人们有机会做正确的事时
When people have the chance to do the right thing,
他们一般会挺身而出
they usually step up.
-人们就  -在你开始唱歌之前
- I mean, people just -- - L-Let me stop you
我先打断你一下  好吗
before you break into song, okay?
顺便说一句
And, by the way,
谁来给这些炮灰训练
who would train all this cannon fodder?
-我来  -给我一周时间
- I will. - Give me a week.
我是反问  好吗
Rhetorical, okay?
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
我再也不想听到关于此事的半个字
I never want to hear another word about any of it, ever.
没了救世军  我们是不是过得更好
Would we be better off without the Saviors,
-是或不是  -是  好吧
- yes or no? - Yeah. Sure. Okay.
那你要怎么解决问题
So, what will you do to fix the problem?
我没说过我们有问题
I didn't say we had a problem.
是你们说的
You did.
在我管辖范围之外发生的事
And what happens outside of my purview
与我无关
is outside of my purview.
搞什么
What the hell, man?
你要么站我们这边  要么不站
You're either with us or you ain't.
你坐在那里见风使舵  嘴里没实话
You're sitting over there talking out of both sides of your mouth.
我想我已经说得很清楚了
I -- I think I've made my position very clear.
我想感谢你们所有人今天没有来
And I want to thank all of you for not being here today
没跟我会面
and not having this meeting with me
出去时也别让人看见了
or -- or being seen on your way out.
换句话说  从后门走
In other words, go out the back.
-懦夫  -真想打掉那蠢货的牙齿
- Walking ballsack. - ?Wanna knock that idiot's teeth out.
反正我们也不需要他
Yeah, well, we don't need him anyway.
没错
Yeah, that's right.
因为我们有玛姬  萨沙和耶稣
'Cause we have Maggie and Sasha and Jesus here.
还有
And...
伊妮德
Enid.
-嗨  -怎么了
- Hey, um -- - What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
只是
Just...
出来吧
Come outside.
怎么了
What's going on?
如果你不记得了  我是伯蒂
So, if you don't remember, I'm Bertie.
你们救了我两次命
And I owe my life to you all, twice over.
我们许多人都被救过
A bunch of us do.
伊妮德说你们想说服格雷戈里
Enid says that you want Gregory
让我们跟你们一起对抗救世军
to get us to fight the Saviors with you.
这是真的吗
Is that true?
-是的  -你觉得我们能赢吗
- Yes. ?- Do you think we can win,
我们真的能打败他们吗
that we really could beat them?
我们这种人
Us?
是的
I do.
伊妮德说你们能训练我们
Well, Enid says you could show us the way.
-我准备好了  -我也是
- I'm ready. - Me too.
-是啊  -开始吧
-Yeah. -Let's do this.
-开始吧  -我加入
- Let's do it. - I'm in.
-这是个开始  -我们会找到更多人
- It's a start. - We'll get more.
-还是不够  -是啊
- It still won't be enough. - No, it won't.
只要找到合适的东西
Well, we find the right stuff,
也许根本不需要以人数取胜
then maybe we don't need the numbers.
炸飞他们  烧死他们
Blow 'em up, burn 'em to the ground.
你说过救世军里不仅有士兵
You said there weren't just soldiers with the Saviors,
还有工人
that there were workers there.
别无选择的人们
People didn't have a choice.
我们必须赢
We gotta win.
我们需要更多人手  另一个社区
We need more hands, another group.
尼根有前哨站
Negan has outposts.
地形和距离都对我们不利
The geography, the distance works against us.
我们得回去
We gotta get back.
如果他们来找达里尔  我们得在
If they come looking for Daryl, we need to be there.
你们没必要回去
You don't have to get back.
现在没必要
Not yet.
这是他们的长距离对讲机
It's one of theirs, long range.
我们可以偷听  了解他们的动态
We can listen in, keep track of them.
如果我们不回去  那我们做什么
So, if we're not going back, what are we doing, then?
是时候让你们见以西结了
I think it's time we introduced you to Ezekiel.
以西结国王
King Ezekiel.
国王
King?
那里叫神之国吗
It's called "The Kingdom"?
是啊
Yeah.
名不是我取的
I didn't name it.
还有多远
How much farther?
严格说来  我们已经到了
Well, technically, we're already here.
我是说  我们一直在这里
I mean, we're always here,
但我们到了  神之国
but here we are -- at the Kingdom.
这里是它的外围
Well, its outer edge.
我们等什么呢
Hey, what the hell we waitin' on?
等他们
Waiting for them.
何人胆敢擅闯神之国领土...
Who dares to trespass on the sovereign land of the --
靠
Oh, shit.
耶稣  是你吗
Jesus, is that you?
这些人是谁  保罗
Who are all these people, Paul?
你好呀  理查德
Hi, Richard.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
我也很高兴见到你
It's good to see you, too.
你的这些朋友们是什么人
Your friends, who are they?
这位是瑞克・格兰姆斯
This is Rick Grimes.
他是一个和我们志同道合的社区的首领
He's the leader of a like-minded community.
这些是他的一部分人马
These are some of his people.
我们想觐见以西结国王
We would like to request an audience with King Ezekiel.
下车
Get out of the car.
你说他们是...志同道合的社区
You say they're a... like-minded community.
怎么个志同道合法
Like-minded how?
我们求生  做交易  和行尸战斗
We live, we trade, we fight the dead.
有时也和别的东西战斗
Sometimes others.
排好队
Line up.
行了  这就是在浪费时间
Okay. This is a waste of time.
走吧  我们回去
Come on. Let's go.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
国王很繁忙
The King is a busy man.
而这又是个危机四伏的世界
And it's a dangerous world.
我们一般不会让一群陌生人
We don't usually allow a pack of strangers
随意迈进我们的大门
to waltz through our door.
我们想让这个世界不那么危机四伏
We want to make the world less dangerous,
我们都是过来向国王表明
and we are all here to show the King
我们的认真程度的
how serious we are about that.
把车留在外面
The car stays outside.
枪支上缴
You gotta hand over your guns.
我们就两把枪
We only have two.
好了
Okay.
跟我来
Follow me.
进去之前我想说
Before we go in,
你有勇有谋
you have a brain and a backbone,
所以我和你谈  而不是格雷戈里
so I'm talking to you, not Gregory.
无论你这次来是为了什么
Whatever you're trying to start here,
为了另一条庇护协议  或是交易
another protection pact, a trade,
但这些都毫无意义
none of it matters
除非我们着手处理真正的问题...
if we don't start dealing with the real problem --
救世军
the Saviors.
理查德  我从来没见你笑过
You know, Richard, I've never seen you smile.
这一点今天可能要改变了
I think that's gonna change today.
他们人数是挺多的
They have the numbers.
但他们能战斗吗
But can they fight?
妥妥的
Oh, they can fight.
也许吧
Maybe.
摩根
Morgan?
你们是怎么认识的
How do you know each other?
灾变刚开始我们就认识了
We go back to the start.
国王准备好接见你们了
Well, the King is ready to see you.
-你找到卡萝尔了吗  -找到了
- Did you find Carol? - I did, yeah.
她人呢  她没出事吧
Where is she? Is she okay?
她之前在这里  后来离开了
She was here, and then she left.
她不满我跟着她
You know, she wasn't too happy, me following her.
她想远离我们  远离所有人
She wanted to get away from us, from everyone.
但我找到她时  她中枪了
But when I found her, she was shot.
只是擦伤  我把她带回了这里
It was just a graze. I got her back here.
这里有医生  挺厉害的
They got doctors. They're good.
是他们干的吗
Was it them?
是的
It was.
她与他们中几人发生了冲突
She had crossed with some of them,
然后其中一个跟着她  想要杀了她
and one of them followed her, tried to kill her,
但我阻止了他
but I stopped him.
我杀了他
I killed him.
我必须这么做
I had to.
卡萝尔之前在这里的
Carol was here.
她得到了帮助
She got help.
如今她离开了
Now she's gone.
耶稣
Jesus!
很高兴见到你  老朋友
It pleases me to see you, old friend.
-他确实很高兴  -杰瑞
- It pleases him, indeed! - Jerry.
告诉我
Tell me,
你给好国王以西结带来了什么消息
what news do you bring good King Ezekiel?
这些你是给我带来的新盟友吗
Are these new allies you've brought me?
确实是的  陛下
Indeed, they are, Your Majesty.
这位是...
This is...
对了  我忘了和你们说...
Oh, right. I forgot to mention that --
对  有只老虎
Yeah, a tiger.
这位是瑞克・格兰姆斯
This is Rick Grimes,
亚历山大的首领
the leader of Alexandria,
这些是他的一部分人马
and these are some of his people.
欢迎各位来到神之国  旅人们
I welcome you all to the Kingdom, good travelers.
你们为何来到我们美丽的国土
Now, what brings you to our fair land?
你们为何求见本王
Why do you seek an audience with the King?
以西结...
Ezekiel --
以西结...国王
King...Ezekiel.
亚历山大
Alexandria,
山顶寨
the Hilltop,
神之国...
and the Kingdom --
我们这三个社区有一个共同点
all three of our communities have something in common.
我们都供奉救世军
We all serve the Saviors.
亚历山大曾和他们干过一架
Alexandria already fought them once,
我们赢了
and we won.
我们以为自己解决了威胁
We thought we took out the threat,
但我们那时没有摸清敌情
but we don't know then what we know now.
我们只是端掉了一个哨站
We only beat one outpost.
我们得知你和他们做了交易
We've been told you have a deal with them,
你了解他们
that you know them.
那你一定知道
Then you know
他们是用暴力和恐惧进行统治的
they rule through violence and fear.
陛下  我只告诉了他们...
Your Majesty, I only told them of the --
我的人民并不知道我们和救世军的交易...
Our deal with the Saviors is not known among my people --
这是有正当理由的
for good cause.
因为你和我们说了山顶寨所受的苦
We made you a party to that secret
我们才向你透露了那个秘密
when you told us of the Hilltop's own travails,
但我们没想到你会向别人泄密...
but we did not expect you to share --
我们可以互相帮助
We can help each other.
不准打断国王
Don't interrupt the King.
我们信任你
We brought you into our confidence.
你为何要破坏这份信任
Why did you break it?
因为我想让你听听瑞克的计划
Because I want you to hear Rick's plans.
你有何计划呢
And what plans have you,
亚历山大的瑞克・格兰姆斯
Rick Grimes of Alexandria?
我们来此请求神之国  请求你
We came to ask the Kingdom, to ask you,
加入我们  一起反抗救世军
to join us in fighting the Saviors,
为所有人的自由而战
fighting for freedom for all of us.
你的请求很危险
What you are asking is very serious.
我们有好几个人  他们都是好人
Several of our people -- good people...
被救世军残忍杀害了
were killed by the Saviors, brutally.
谁
Who?
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
格伦
Glenn.
斯宾塞  奥利维亚
Spencer, Olivia.
尤金被劫走了
Eugene was taken.
他们也劫持过达里尔
They took Daryl.
他逃了出来
He escaped.
只要他没被抓回去  他就是个目标
Every second he's out here, he's a target.
你想说自己是对的吗
You gonna say you were right?
不
No.
我
I'm...
他们的死  我非常遗憾
I'm just real sorry they're gone.
尼根杀害了格伦和亚伯拉罕
Negan murdered Glenn and Abraham,
活活砸死了他们
beat them to death.
恐吓山顶寨
Terrorized the Hilltop,
放出行尸  只为立威
set loose walkers just to make a point.
我曾以为我们能忍受他们的协议
I used to think the deal was something we could live with.
很多人都这样以为
A lot of us did.
但情况变了
But that's changing.
所以让我们改变世界吧  陛下
So let's change the world, Your Majesty.
我想坦白说出我们的请求
I want to be honest about what we're asking.
我的人很强  但人手不够
My people are strong, but there's not enough of us.
我们没枪  至少不够
We don't have guns... not enough, at least.
没有足够的武器  就这样
Not a lot of weapons, period.
我们有人手
We have people.
也有武器
And weapons.
如果我们联盟  先下手为强  就能打败他们
If we strike first, together, we can beat them.
陛下
Your Majesty,
不要再等着事情发展到
no more waiting for things to get worse
不可收拾的地步了
beyond what we can handle.
我们要扭转事态
We set things right.
时机正好
The time is now.
摩根  你怎么看
Morgan, what say you?
我
Me?
说吧
Speak.
会死人
People will die.
会死很多人  不仅是救世军  还有...
A lot of people, and not just the Saviors. It...
如果能找到更好的办法
If we can find another way,
必须找到
we have to.
也许只是尼根的问题
Maybe it's just about Negan...
只要抓住他  扣住他
just capturing him, holding him.
也许
Maybe...
我
I...
时候不早了
The hour grows late.
亚历山大的瑞克・格兰姆斯
Rick Grimes of Alexandria...
国王要深思你的话
you have given the King much to ponder.
在我小时候
Well, when I was a kid,
妈妈给我讲过一个故事
my mother told me a story.
从前有条通向王国的路
There was a road to a kingdom,
路中间嵌着一块大石头
and there was a rock in the road.
人们只是绕着它走
And people would just avoid it,
而马匹会被绊到  伤到腿而死
but horses would break their legs on it and die,
马车轮子会脱落
wagon wheels would come off.
人们损失了很多要卖的货物
People would lose the goods they'd be coming to sell.
一个小女孩就遇到了这种事
That's what happened to a little girl.
她自家酿的啤酒桶掉了下来
The cask of beer her family brewed fell right off.
摔坏了
It broke.
酒都渗进土里  没了
Dirt soaked it all up, and it was gone.
那是她家最后的指望
That was her family's last chance.
他们挨饿  没钱买吃的
They were hungry. They didn't have any money.
她只能坐在那里哭  但是
She just... sat there and cried, but...
她不明白为什么石头还在那
...she wondered why it was still there...
伤害着其他人
for it to hurt someone else.
所以她用双手去挖石头  直到血流不止
So she dug at that rock in the road with her hands till they bled,
用尽力气把它搬了出来
used everything she had to pull it out.
花了好几个小时
It took hours.
然后
And then...
当她准备填坑的时候
...when she was gonna fill it up,
她看到坑里有东西
she saw something in it.
是一袋金子
It was a bag of gold.
真好
All right.
是国王埋下的那块石头
The king had put that rock in the road
因为他知道  肯挖出它的人
because he knew the person who dug it out,
肯动手的人
who did something,
他们值得受奖
they deserved a reward.
他们值得过上
They deserved to have their life
更好的生活  直到永远
changed for the good.... forever.
我邀请你们共进晚餐
I invite you all to sup with us
并留宿到明天
and stay till the morrow.
我们得回去
Yeah, we need to get back home.
清晨我会降旨
I shall deliver my decree in the morn.
抱歉
Sorry.
我
I...
抱歉
Sorry.
我以为是行尸
I thought you were one of the dead.
你为什么不掉头跑掉
Why didn't you just run the other way?
我  我在训练
Well, I'm...I'm training.
逼迫自己
I'm pushing myself,
直面困难
trying to step up.
把保险上好
Put the safety back on.
我在练习射击
Practicing shooting.
给你点建议
Let me give you some advice.
天快黑了
It's gonna be dark soon.
别一个人溜达
Don't wander around out here on your own.
会没命的
You'll get yourself killed.
你也不该转悠  不是吗
Same goes for you, too, right?
你不是我
You're not me.
回家吧  本杰明
Go home, Benjamin.
-那个  我  -什么
- Well, I...Wha...  - ?What?
以西结会时常来看望你
Ezekiel's gonna keep coming out here to check on you.
他不想打扰你
He doesn't want to bug you,
但他得知道你是否还好
but he needs to know that you're okay.
他跟你说的吗
He told you that?
不是
No.
但我了解他
But I know him.
那就告诉他...
Well, tell him...
我不能
I can't.
他对在意的人都会照料倍至
He looks out for the people that he cares about.
你想要吃的吗
Do you want some food?
或者水
A bottle of water?
我多带了一些以防碰到有需要的人
I carry extra in case I run into someone who needs it.
为什么
Why?
因为人已经所剩不多了
There's not a lot of us left.
得互相帮助
Have to help each other.
或许还会再见到你
Maybe I'll see you again.
或许吧
Maybe.
在外面脚步要轻
Heel-toe, heel-toe out here.
膝盖弯着走
Bend at your knees.
你得安静点
You want to keep quiet.
老远就听到你了
I heard you from a mile away.
好
Okay.
待一切开始时
And when this happens,
待自由之声响起时
and when we allow freedom to ring...
响彻每个村庄  每个小镇
when we let it ring from every village and every hamlet,
每个州  每个城市时
from every state and every city,
我们将能加速那一天的到来
we will be able to speed up that day
那时  上帝的所有子民
when all of God's children,
黑人和白人
black men and white men,
犹太人和非犹太人  新教徒和天主教徒
Jews and Gentiles, Protestants and Catholics,
能携手并进
will be able to join hands
合唱那首古老的黑人灵歌
and sing in the words of the old Negro spiritual --
终于自由了  终于自由了
Free at last, Free at last!
感谢全能的上帝
Thank God Almighty,
我们...终于自由了
we are...free at last.
谢谢你今天来帮我讲故事
Thanks for stepping in on story duty.
我来道晚安
I stopped in to say good night.
你没来吃晚餐  你去哪了
You missed supper. Where were you?
去林子里散了散步
Went for a walk in the woods.
你出去了
You went out there?
-没人陪同吗  -是的
- Unaccompanied? - ?Yeah.
回来的路上干掉了两个行尸
Took out two dead ones on my way back.
棍子使得不错了
Getting pretty good with the stick.
想练练枪法
Wanted to practice with the gun.
我看到卡萝尔在外面
I, saw Carol out there.
她看起来还好吗
Did she, uh...seem well?
-你跟她说话了吗  -说了
- Did -- Did you talk to her? ?- Yeah.
她问我为什么带着食物和水
She asked why I carry food and water
以防遇到别人
in case I run into people.
你告诉她了吗
And you told her?
那也是为什么我们该答应瑞克
It's the same reason we should say yes to Rick.
说来听听
Elaborate.
你看到了他们的眼神
You saw their eyes.
有没有我们的帮助  他们都会搏命的
They're gonna risk everything if we help them or not.
如果我们不帮他们  对他们置之不理
And if we don't help them, if we turn away,
他们就赢不了
then they can't win.
假设他们赢了
And if they do, somehow...
他们就救了我们
they will have saved us,
我们什么也不用干
and we won't have done a thing.
我爸爸常说
My dad always said
要是有人让你去逞英雄
that if you're asked to be the hero,
那就去逞
be a hero.
你想让我对一切都做好准备  我准备好了
You wanted me to be ready for anything, and I am.
我们准备好了
We are.
感谢你的建议
I thank you for your sage counsel.
你父亲会非常骄傲的
Your father would be very proud.
国王很骄傲
The King is very proud.
这就是这里的生活
This is life here.
每一天
Every day.
但这是有代价的
But it came at a cost.
我曾想要更多
And I wanted more of this.
我曾想要扩张
I wanted to expand.
建造更多像这里一样的地方
To create more places like this.
人们失去了四肢
Men and women lost their limbs.
孩子们失去了双亲
Children lost their parents
因为我在没必要的时候
because I sent them into battle against the wasted
派他们去与行尸作战
when I did not need to.
这次不同
This is different.
并不是
It isn't.
这次不同
It is.
行尸不会统治支配我们
The dead don't rule us.
外面的世界跟墙内截然不同
The world doesn't look like this outside your walls.
人们过得没这么好
People don't have it as good.
有些人过得凄惨之至
Some people don't have it good at all.
我只能为我的子民考虑
I have to worry about my people.
你称自己为国王
You call yourself a damn king.
却一点没有国王的样子
You sure as hell don't act like one.
这一切
All of this...
都有代价
came at a cost.
是用生命  残肢断臂换来的
It was lives, arms, legs.
和救世军的和平并不稳定
The peace we have with the Saviors is uneasy,
但起码是和平
but it is peace.
我得把握住
I have to hold on to it.
我得尝试
I have to try.
尽管神之国不能提供你们需要的协助
Although the Kingdom cannot grant you the aid you desire,
但国王同情你的困境
the King is sympathetic to your plight.
我可以为友人达里尔提供庇护
I offer our friend Daryl asylum
他想留多久都行
for as long as he requires it.
他在这里很安全
He will be safe here.
救世军不会进入我们的围墙
The Saviors do not set foot inside our walls.
你觉得这种情况能撑多久
How long do you think that's gonna last?
我知道会发生什么
I knew what was coming.
我知道那个国王会拒绝
I knew that King guy would say no.
但我还是很生气
But it still pissed me off.
你跟我讲这个干什么
What the hell are you telling me for?
我们睡过同一个死人
We both had sex with the same dead guy.
不代表我们是朋友了
It doesn't make us friends.
你能改变他的心意  但你不愿这么做
You can change his mind, but you won't.
那你可以留下来
Then you can stay.
我们聊聊
We can talk.
我们有多少人
How many people do we have?
能战斗的
To fight?
我跟你们走
I'll go with you.
我们连从正面
We don't even have enough
攻下一个哨站的人手都不够
to take on one outpost face-to-face yet.
所以神之国必须加入进来
So the Kingdom has to get involved,
否则救世军会一直掌管一切
or the Saviors will always be in charge.
不是士兵的问题
It isn't about soldiers.
是我们使他们变得更强
We're making them stronger.
给他们的食物越多
The more food we give them,
武器越多  或者任何东西更多
the more arms, the more everything,
每天我们中有人给他上贡
every day any of us give them something,
他们就会变得越难被打败
they become harder and harder to beat.
好了  开门  我们走
All right, open it up. We're gone.
你不能走
You're not.
我不能留在这
I'm not staying here.
你必须留下
You have to.
这是最聪明的做法
It's the smartest play.
你心里清楚
You know it is.
试着跟以西结谈谈
Try to talk to Ezekiel.
或者一直盯着他直到他妥协
Or stare him into submission --
不管用什么方法
Whatever it takes.
我们很快回来
We'll be back soon.
致所有
For anyone out there
和我一样爱那个肥鬼的人
who loved the obese bastard as much as I did,
我只想说几句
I just want to say a few words.
肥乔不是最牛逼的那个
Fat Joey was not the most badass son of bitch,
但是他很忠诚
but he was loyal.
他很幽默
He had a great sense of humor.
实际上前两天我们还在开玩笑
In fact, we were just joking about oral sex
和露西尔口交
with Lucille the other day.
他死了一切都不一样了
Things will not be the same now that he's dead.
没了肥乔
Without Fat Joey,
瘦乔就只是乔了
Skinny Joey is just Joey.
真他妈悲催
So it's a goddamn tragedy.
让我们默哀片刻
So, let's have a moment of silence.
有人想挡路
Someone's trying to block the way.
肯定是救世军
Gotta be the Saviors.
看
Look.
我想那是他们的基地
I think that's their base over there.
是的
Yeah, that's it.
一定是想让别人难接近他们
Must be trying to make it hard to get to them.
我们得前进
We gotta keep going.
我们移开车  然后再移回来
We'll move them, and then we'll move them back.
他们不会知道我们来过
They don't need to know we were here.
瑞克
Rick.
来看看
Come take a look at this.
这是为了什么
What's all this for?
等等
Wait.
我在卡车后面藏着的时候
When I was hiding in the back of the truck,
听到有几个人讨论
I heard a couple of them talking about this.
是为尸群准备的
This is for a herd.
所以用的是钢索
That's why it's a steel cable.
不只是为了一只行尸
It's not just for one walker.
是为很多
It's for a lot.
我们需要这些炸药
We need these explosives.
是的
Yeah.
但首先我们得想办法拆除
But we have to figure out how to disarm it first.
好吧
Okay.
如果这东西爆炸
Backing up is not gonna make a difference
后退也没用
if this thing goes off.
出现红色事件
We got ourselves a red situation.
派一支搜索队
I need a search party.
看看达里尔有没有犯傻跑回家
See if Daryl ran home like the dumb animal that he is.
就去办  午饭前赶到
On it. Be there in time for lunch.
把那个小破地儿掘地三尺
Turn that sleepy little burg upside down.
我们该走了
We gotta go.
我们得在他们之前回去  但我们需要这些
We gotta get there before them, but we need these.
-我们得清出一条路  -是
- We need to clear a path anyway. - Yeah.
罗西塔
Rosita?
第一部分完成
First part's done.
现在呢  我们得拆掉次级炸药
What now? We gotta unwrap the secondary explosives --
炸药  火箭筒
the dynamite, the RPGs.
确保别装混了
Make sure these casings are not messed up,
也不要乱动
and do not mess them up, either.
这些东西还能炸
This thing could still blow.
都听到了  行动
You all heard her. Let's go.
把完好的炸药装上车
You can load the explosives into the trunk as long as they're in good shape.
不能有凹痕和撕裂  它们没激活
No dents, no tears. They're not live.
还需要被触发引爆
They still need to be triggered to be set off.
别拿这个
Not that one.
-看起来不对劲  -好
- I don't like the way it looks. - Okay.
爸
Dad.
看
Look.
好  它们在那
Okay. There they are.
但还远
But they're far.
我们还有时间
We still have time.
确定吗
You sure?
我们需要这些
We need these.
我们得把车放回斜坡前面
And we need to get the cars back in front of the onramp.
他们会知道我们拿了炸药  有什么用呢
They'll know we took their explosives, so does it matter?
-我们要让尸群留在公路上  -为什么
- We want that herd to stay on the highway. - ?Why?
我们也许会用到
We may need it.
好了  塔拉  卡尔  快来
Okay. Tara, Carl, come on!
瑞克
Uh...Rick...
好了
All right.
萨沙  耶稣
Sasha, Jesus,
你们可以走回山顶寨吗
can you get back to the Hilltop on foot?
可以
Yeah.
告诉玛姬我们不会放弃
Tell Maggie we're not giving up.
走
Go!
给
Here.
我们需要每一根炸药  火箭弹
We need every stick, every RPG.
好
Yeah.
瑞克
Rick.
它们会堵死他们
They're gonna cut them off.
我们分头走吧
Can we just split up?
不行
No.
车
The cars.
如果能开动的话...
If they run...
我们启动的时候鸣笛
We lay on the horn when we start it --
我挥下手一起走  好的
I'll bring my arm down, and we go. ?Yes.
跟上来
Stay together!
-该死  -我们会想办法
- Damn it! ?- We'll figure it out.
我就说看起来不对劲
Yeah, I didn't like the look of that shit at all.
是我硬要做的
I pushed it.
我们在这
We're here.
你可以笑了
You can smile.
我们成功了
We made it.
我们可以做到
We can make it.
我们可以
We can.
我们是活下来的人
We're the ones who live.
车扔了吗
Lose the car?
在安全的地方
Uh, it's somewhere safe.
-你什么都没找到  -没有
- You didn't find anything. ?- No.
听着  我们得让所有人准备好
Listen, we need to get everyone ready.
救...
The--
瑞克  你好
Rick. Hello.
还有  再次你好
And...hello again.
想着你们不会这么快来
We thought it'd be longer.
你以为我们来收贡品吗
Do you think we're here for a tribute?
是不是
Do you?
还有别的原因吗
Is there another reason?
有
There is.
我们来找达里尔
We're here for Daryl.
可尼根抓走了达里尔
But Negan took Daryl.
但是你儿子来了
Oh, but... then your son showed up,
达里尔就失踪了
Daryl went missing --
也许这两件事有关
might those two things be connected?
没关
They're not.
我们现在才知道他逃跑了
We didn't know he was gone till right now.
那就简单了
Then this should be easy.
现在  每人找一人
Now, everyone find a buddy.
跟我们走
Gonna have to follow us around.
如果他在这
If he's here,
我们要确保让你们亲眼看他死
we really need you all to see him die.
天啊
Wow.
架子空空如也
These are some bare shelving units.
你们办了烧烤
You guys have a barbecue or something
没叫我们吗
and not invite us?
真的  太悲哀了
Seriously, this is sad.
希望你们没有藏东西
Hope you're not trying to hide stuff from us,
因为那通常没好下场
'cause that generally doesn't go over very well.
我们人很多
We have a lot of people.
找东西越来越难
It's...getting harder to find stuff,
我们最近的重心是寻找
and our focus lately has been on finding things
尼根要的东西
that Negan might want.
我们还在适应新体制
We're still adjusting to the new system.
我们今天会找到更多
We were gonna scavenge more today.
如果你愿意等  我们会带东西回来
If you just wait, we'll...bring something back.
我们会找到更多
We'll find more.
放松
Relax.
我不是来收贡的
I'm not here for a pick-up.
这是好事
Good thing.
但那天快到了
But that day is coming,
所以你们最好做该做的事
so you best do whatever you need to.
好好找
Dig deep.
加倍努力
Go the extra mile.
冒一下险
Take some risks!
我们会的
We will.
我们会感激的
Well, we will appreciate that.
感谢你的合作  瑞克
Thank you for the cooperation, Rick.
抱歉把这里搞乱了
My apologies for leaving the place a bit of a mess,
但是我们还有其他屁事要去做
but we got a litany of other shit to attend to.
我猜你也是
So do you, I guess.
抓紧
Tick-tock.
快点
Chop-chop.
还有  瑞克
Oh! And, Rick...
如果达里尔真在这里出现
if Daryl does turn up here
两天后  两个月后
two days from now, two months from now...
见鬼  两年后
hell, two years from now,
你要知道这事没有诉讼时效
just know there's no statute of limitations on this.
把斧子放在手边
Keep that hatchet handy.
如果他在你们这出现  你会用上的
You're gonna need it if he turns up with you people.
这次可不会像你儿子那次一样了
And it won't turn out the way it did for your boy.
储藏室怎么了
What happened to the pantry?
不清楚
We don't know.
我们得谈谈加百利
And we need to talk about Gabriel.
他在哪
Where is he?
你们去找物资的那晚  他在值班
He was on watch the night you all went to scavenge.
我和他本来应该早上换班
I was supposed to take over for him in the morning.
他没在哨岗上
He wasn't at his post.
储藏室被清空了  少了一辆车
Pantry was cleared out and a car was gone.
没人再看到过他
No one's seen him since.
那个杂种
That son of a bitch.
-他偷东西跑掉了  -看起来是这样
- He stole our shit and ran. - ?That's...what it looks like.
-我不想相信  -我不相信
- Well, I don't want to believe it. - I don't believe it.
加百利不是那样的人
That's not Gabriel.
他不会那样对我们
He wouldn't do that to us.
我也以为他变了
I thought he changed, too,
但没有其他可能
but it can't be anything else.
有的
Yes, it can.
不敢相信他会带我们的东西跑掉
I can't believe he would just take our stuff and go.
他不是那样的人
I mean, that's -- that's not who he is.
他看到奥利维亚和斯宾塞死了
Well, he saw Olivia and Spencer die
就在他面前
right in front of him.
我知道  我只是...
I know. I just...
他找到了勇气  知道吗
He found his courage, you know?
我真心希望他能坚持住
I want to believe he held on to it.
他为什么不带走这个
Why wouldn't he have taken this with him?
他为什么丢在地板上
Why would he leave it on the floor?
外面没有之前的痕迹
There weren't tracks out there before.
我们没找到什么
We didn't find anything now.
也许达里尔能发现些什么
Maybe Daryl could've picked something up.
他走了
He left.
没留纸条
He didn't leave a note.
显然不想被找到
He obviously doesn't want to be found.
他想的
Yes, he does.
船
他怎么知道我们去过那里
How would he know we were out there?
我不知道
I don't know.
就这样吗
So that's it?
你终于要离开我了
You're finally leaving me?
被你发现了
You caught me.
我只是
I'm just...
厌倦了在家里的快乐
sick of being so damn happy at home, you know?
不知道该怎么跟你说
Didn't know how to tell you.
亲爱的
Babe --
他们需要我
They need me.
加百利需要我
Gabriel needs me.
如果我问你一件事
If I ask you something,
你能说实话吗
will you tell me the truth?
-当然  -他们不是出去找物资的  对吧
- Of course. - ?The others didn't go out there scavenging, did they?
他们又要抗击了  而他们没告诉我们
They're going after them again, and they're not telling us.
瑞克有他的理由
Rick has his reasons.
瑞克没有被毒打过
Rick didn't get the shit beaten out of him.
你以为这只是去找加百利  但会有更多的事
You think this is about Gabriel, but it's gonna be more.
总会有更多的事
It's always more.
所以拜托了  别走
So, please, please don't go.
加百利是我们的一员
Gabriel's one of us.
我必须去
I have to.
救世军的事  与此无关
What's going on with the Saviors, that isn't this.
如果瑞克要对抗救世军
If Rick is taking on the Saviors,
那一切都有关
that is everything.
如果你们不在的时候他们发现了呢
W-What if they find out while you're gone?
如果他们回来呢
What if they come back here?
你想离开吗
Do you want to leave?
背弃他们吗
Just turn our backs?
我想要我们活着
I want us alive.
两个人都活着
Both of us.
纪念詹姆斯・赫特布雷德尔
[注:亚特兰大电影人  《行尸走肉》道具组成员
深受剧组成员喜爱
2016年11月从片场回家路上遇车祸去世]